Let's go get changed, so we can go.
I'm getting tired.
It made me see clearly
where I really belong.
Because my son's made the same mistake.
That's why I'm worried about Mr. Thee,
since I'm a mother like you.
If you can't make Ms. Mook happy,
then you should let her go.
This is my problem.
I can deal with it myself.
Mook.
Here are the photos reshot yesterday
for you to choose from.
You know, you don't have to do this, Mook.
- I'll go talk to my--
- It's not an issue for us.
We're happy to edit our work
as our clients see fit.
If you really want to help,
please choose the photos
and finalize this project.
No! Wait, Mr.--
Why'd you remove Ms. Narin
from her position?
How could you do this?
I'm a co-investor,
and I'm the hotel's majority shareholder.
I have the authority to replace the board.
It's perfectly normal.
I might even consider
more ways of restructuring soon.
But when we made the deal,
you never mentioned this.
Well, this is what I want to do now.
Do you have a problem with that?
I don't.
I'm just thinking of a way
to tell Ms. Narin.
Don't worry about it.
I'll handle it myself.
Got it, Mr. Thee.
Why'd you remove Ms. Narin?
Or did you buy up all the shares to…
Let's go over our work.
Is Boss not here, Mr. Suetrong?
Oh, he left this afternoon.
I heard he had to take care of something,
and he won't be back.
Is it urgent?
I have to talk to him about work.
I'll just do it later.
- A little to the left.
- Left?
Left, please.
- Is that good?
- A little more.
Wait. A little to the right.
To the right, and up a bit.
Okay.
- Is that good?
- Yes.
Here, I'll help.
Thanks.
- Make sure it's straight.
- Good?
Yes.
This is my husband's old house.
I'll use this place
for storing campaign materials
and to hold meetings with the staff,
so we won't have to bother
using our party's office.
Sounds like a good idea, Prao.
Let's go.
This is Pat's car.
Does it match?
Did I arrange them right?
Hey, your face got dirty.
Hold on. You're making it worse.
Let me get it for you.
It's all over your face.
Pat!
Prao.
I just caught you red-handed.
Still got any excuses?
Caught what?
Well, I caught you and Pat
messing around here, of course!
Then, you've misunderstood us.
We haven't even gone that far yet.
Please show a little respect.
You want respect?
Then you shouldn't have been so obnoxious!
You're some big shot's daughter,
and I heard you're engaged, even,
yet you're here alone with my husband?
How shameless!
Calm down, Prao.
If you maintained your relationship,
no one could take him from you.
Well, does your fiancé know about this?
Or perhaps
he's also a homewrecker like you!
Enough, Prao. Stop disrespecting others.
We have to talk.
Pat! What the hell? Let go!
- Let go of me, Pat.
- Prao.
You've misunderstood me, Prao.
Can you listen to me for a change?
You two were alone together,
yet you're saying I misunderstood you?
Bell asked to rent the house
and use it as her studio.
I figured it's vacant anyway,
so I let her rent it.
It's not what you think.
Before, when people wanted to rent it,
you didn't allow it.
So how come you let her?
Because she values this house, Prao,
whereas you never cared about it.
You didn't even bother to come here.
I'm using the house
as my dad's temporary office,
so please tell her to move out!
This house is mine,
so it's my call what I do with it.
Are you that crazy over her, Pat?!
Fine.
You can let her rent the house
if you want.
But on one condition.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I apologize on her behalf.
I'm okay.
I understand how your wife feels.
She saw you with me, so she got jealous
and couldn't control her emotions.
It's not your fault at all, though.
Prao and I have had issues
for a very long time.
Clarity can make everything better,
but it can only be better
if you know what your heart wants.
Please give me some more time.
How are you going to handle this?
Fine. You can let her
rent the house if you want.
But on one condition.
You have to join my dad's party
and run for office.
Hey, I'm good with whatever you decide.
I'll leave if I'm making
you uncomfortable.
You aren't making me uncomfortable.
You just helped me with my decision.
Okay.
Whan, the pictures Mr. Thee chose
are in here.
Edit them and run
the artworks by me first.
- Okay.
It's just…
I was just reviewing
the photos we had from before,
in case there's any that we can use.
Whan, can you zoom in
on that kid on the board?
- Try zooming in.
- Okay.
Done.
Whan, can you send me this photo?
Mook.
Uh, Mook?
May, where is she rushing off to?
Who knows? I'm right here with you.
We should let her be for now.
She probably still can't move on.
PIAMSUK ORPHANAGE
Hello. Can I help you with anything?
- Hello, Teacher.
- Hello.
I've been here before. Do you remember me?
Oh, Ms. Mook.
You were with Mr. Thee, right?
Yes. I wanted to ask you about something.
I was wondering, what's the name
of the boy in the photo,
and where is he now?
I just so happened to find a photo
of a kid who looked similar,
so I wanted to find out
if it's the same kid.
And where did you find that photo?
At the house of an acquaintance.
Her name's Narin.
- Could you tell me about his background--
- Sorry, Ms. Mook.
I'm very sorry.
We have a rule against
disclosing information
of the children here to outsiders.
Then, can I at least know his name?
It's Ake. His name is Ake.
Thank you.
I've taken up enough of your time,
so if you'll excuse me.
- Goodbye.
Thank you for always
remembering this place, Saifah.
And I couldn't be happier to see
that you're living such a great life.
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be where I am now.
I'm happy to do anything
to make those children happy.
Teacher,
could you do me a favor?
If anyone asks about me,
can you cover for me?
Even if you didn't ask,
I would do it anyway.
Mrs. Anna told me right from the start
not to tell anyone about your background.
But I've never forgotten
who I am, where I come from,
and how certain people have hurt me.
PIAMSUK ORPHANAGE
Ms. Mook came here yesterday.
She brought your childhood photo
and asked me who the kid was.
I didn't tell her anything, though.
I even lied and said his name was Ake.
FAVORITES
MOOK - MR. PITAK
I'll handle it from here.
- I really appreciate it, Teacher.
- No problem.
Why are you here?
We don't have a meeting today.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see Ms. Narin.
There's more work I'd like you to edit.
You could've called me or mailed me.
You shouldn't be here
unless it's important.
I don't want any more trouble.
Did you go to Piamsuk Orphanage?
How'd you know?
I was talking to Ms. Tassanee
about the grant for the kids.
She told me you went there yesterday.
What were you doing there?
I had something to take care of.
Is it my job to tell you about it?
Come on. Let's talk about work.
Please let me know
what you'd like me to edit.
Mr. Thee.
- Hello.
- Hello, Mr. Pat.
- Are you here to see Mook?
- Yes.
Do you have a minute?
I wanted to talk to you about something.
RUAM JAI PARTY - COLLABORATE
AND HELP IMPROVE THE THAI SOCIETY
Why isn't Pat here yet?
Are you sure
he'll be able to apply in time?
Yes, I am. I offered him a deal.
You can let her rent the house
if you want.
But on one condition.
You have to join my dad's party
and run for office.
Don't think he'll always cave in
just because you have the upper hand.
When we men don't want something,
we'll never do it.
That much is certain.
But I'm sure Pat's not that kind of guy.
Hello, Mr. Pansak.
Hello! Please, let's go inside.
- Please, go ahead.
- Please, come on in.
- Come on in.
Let's go over the details.
FAVORITES - PAT
I'm sorry, Ms. Narin. I don't understand
why Mr. Thee did this either.
Mr. Thee got the rest
of our hotel's shares
because you helped him,
didn't you, Mr. Chadchai?
I just figured
that if a skilled investor like him
helped run our hotel,
he could get us out of the red.
But I swear I didn't know
he'd remove you from the board like this.
Come on in.
What's up, Boss?
It sure is hard to find you these days.
I wonder if there's something
you haven't told me.
Well, I'm about to tell you now.
I've decided, Mook.
I'm stepping out of my comfort zone.
What do you mean?
I'm divorcing Prao.
What made you come to that decision?
Bell helped me see new perspectives
and gave me the courage
to face my problems.
And I think
I'm not the only one who thinks that.
Who on earth did this?
Prao.
Do you like the way
I decorated the studio?
Why'd you do this, Prao?
Well, you didn't come like you promised.
You humiliated me in front of my dad.
That's what you deserve.
I'm sorry.
This doesn't bother me at all.
This is nothing
compared to what I'm used to.
Okay, I'll take care of it
for you right away.
Yes, thank you.
- Oh, Ms. Mook!
- Good morning, Ms. Narin.
Good morning. You're here so early.
Do you need something?
I heard that Mr. Thee's
removing you from the board.
Yes, Mr. Chadchai informed me.
Mr. Thee will probably
make it official soon.
Have you met him before?
I don't think so.
If you've never met him
or had a conflict with his business,
then why did he do this to you?
To be honest,
I don't quite understand
why he did it either.
But whenever he sees you,
I feel like he…
Doesn't seem to like me, right?
Yes.
I felt it too.
And I feel like I've met him before.
It's strange.
I thought long and hard,
but I couldn't figure it out.
Ms. Narin, I wanted to ask you
about something.
These two boys are my sons.
There was an incident,
and since then, I haven't seen them.
Would you mind telling me what happened?
My two sons and I
lived in a slum.
Even though we were very poor
and had to skip many meals,
we were quite happy.
That is, until the incident happened
that changed my life forever.
That day,
I was out doing some odd jobs.
And after work,
I bought dinner for my kids,
just like I did every day before.
Little did I know that after that,
I'd never get to see my kids again.
Ma'am?
Her blood pressure's normal,
and so is her heart rate.
She's stable now,
but she had a severe concussion
that may cause dementia,
which has to do with memory loss.
It might cause temporary memory loss.
We might need to do another MRI.
But in most cases,
we can get the patient to fully recover,
so please don't worry.
Try looking straight ahead, please.
Does your head hurt?
No, it doesn't.
- What's your name?
- My name is Narin.
Do you remember anything?
For example, where do you live?
How many siblings do you have?
It's alright.
Your memory will gradually recover.
In about two weeks,
we'll be able to start
your physical therapy.
Thank you.
Please get plenty of rest.
Now, move the leg that hurts.
Good. Do your legs hurt?
Easy, okay?
Now step.
Okay.
How are my kids?
Has anyone seen them?
I found out a while ago
that you used to live here
with your children.
When I first got here,
your house was already in this state.
Whoa there.
Tawan, don't fight.
Share with your brother, okay?
- Okay.
- Here.
- Here. Try again.
- Yeah, just like that.
- Whoa.
- Here.
Please calm down, ma'am.
I'll have people help find them.
I'll go to the police,
so they can help find them too,
in case someone knows where they are.
No…
My kids!
Once I recovered,
I tried to find them for many years,
but I never heard from them again.
I don't even know if they're still alive.
To this day,
it's still something
I can't get out of my mind.
What about the person who ran you over?
Mr. Songyod.
He paid all the expenses
and took great care of me
after my recovery.
Ever since I recovered,
we've always stayed in touch
and took care of each other.
Eventually, he asked me to marry him,
and he also had this hotel built.
But unfortunately,
soon after the hotel was finished,
he passed away in an accident.
So you've been running the hotel
for Mr. Songyod?
Yes.
But even after that,
I never stopped searching for my kids.
I've always had hope
that one day I'll meet them before I die.
If you get to see them again,
will you remember them?
It's been so many years.
They must be all grown up now.
I might not remember them.
Ms. Narin, please take a look
at this photo. Here.
Saifah!
Saifah.
It's Saifah. He's my son.
Yes, definitely! It really is him!
Saifah?
Yes, he's Saifah, my eldest son.
Where'd you find this photo?
Please take me there!
- Ms. Narin. Please calm down.
- Ms. Mook.
- Ms. Narin, what's wrong? Ms. Narin!
Help! Somebody help!
Ms. Narin! Ms. Narin!
Please hang in there, Ms. Narin.
Somebody help! Ms. Narin!
Ms. Narin's in this state
partly because of me.
Please don't blame yourself, Mr. Chadchai.
The reason she's in this state
has nothing to do with you.
Well, she got removed from her position
because of me.
I was greedy
for the money Mr. Thee offered.
Did Mr. Thee tell you
why he removed her from her position?
No.
But I swear I didn't know he'd do this.
Ms. Narin is a very caring boss
who takes great care of us.
Our hotel's been
in a severe crisis lately.
I figured if Mr. Thee helped
run the hotel, it'd be good for us,
since he's very skilled.
But we didn't want Ms. Narin
to be removed either.
Can you talk to Mr. Thee for us?
I want to talk to you
about our kids' marriage.
That's a good idea.
They've been engaged for a while now.
I think it's about time.
Should we set a date, then?
I want the wedding to happen
before we sign the contract
for the megaproject.
That way, we'll have
an auspicious ceremony to precede it.
Sounds good.
There won't be a wedding.
Bell and I will not get married.
We don't love each other,
and more importantly,
I already love someone else.
That divorced single mom?
I won't allow it.
You have to marry Bell.
No,
I won't do what I don't want to anymore.
Stop it, Thee.
If you walk out now,
you'll be left with nothing.
I'm sorry, Dad.
When did he find a woman he likes?
I'll handle this. Please don't worry.
Everything will go back to normal.
Thee!
Are you sure you want to do this?
It's time we decided our own path, Bell.
And I'm sure there's someone
who's ready to take care of you
and make you very happy.
What do you mean?
Do you have a minute?
I wanted to talk to you about something.
I love Ms. Bell.
You know,
I'm glad to hear it from your mouth.
So, you aren't angry with me?
Why would I be angry with someone
who loves someone who's like my sister?
Bell is a girl who lacks love and warmth.
I can't give her those things,
but still, I've always looked after her
and cared about her.
But you two are engaged.
You'll have to get married anyway, right?
I won't do it.
And I'm not worried at all
because Bell will get to meet someone good
who can really love her and protect her.
You've known about me
and Mr. Pat all along?
You're my sister. Of course I'd know.
Boss.
Bell?
How come you came with Mr. Pat last night?
It's a long story, Thee.
You're done, right?
Want to leave together?
Let's go get changed so we can go.
I'm getting a bit tired.
Mr. Pat's a sweet man.
But he's still got a bond.
He needs to handle things properly.
If he still can't do it,
I won't let you get involved with him.
But I can tell
that Mr. Pat's serious about you, Bell.
Are you sure your mom
will give in that easily?
I've decided,
and I'm ready to accept the consequences.
Suetrong, about the budget request…
One second.
Is Pat here?
Mr. Pat…
Oh no.
She just got here,
but I can already feel the steam boiling.
So you're finally in your office?
I thought you'd be somewhere
with her again.
If you're here
to talk nonsense, then leave.
Go see my dad with me, now.
You need to apologize
for standing him up that day.
I never told you I'd go.
How dare you go against me?
I won't do
what you want me to anymore, Prao.
If only I had been more firm,
our love life wouldn't have fallen apart.
Let's get divorced
and get it over with, Prao.
POONPUN'S SCHOOL
Hello?
Got it. I'll be right over.
Pun's teacher said he had a fight
with his friend at school.
I'm glad you're both here.
What happened, Teacher?
- Poonpun punched his friend in class.
- No way.
Poonpun's a good kid. He'd never do that.
I'm his mother.
I know what my son is like.
Actually, he wasn't like this before.
He used to be so happy and cheerful.
But lately, he's been keeping to himself.
He's also hot-tempered and violent.
He never does that. I don't believe it.
There are many reasons
for a child's behavioral changes.
For example, his emotions
might be triggered inadvertently.
I invited both of you here today
to ask you if there's been
anything unusual at home,
or if there's been an incident
that was traumatic for your son.
What are you trying to say?
A kid's behavior can change
when they've been exposed to violence,
such as raising your voice,
arguing, or fighting,
all of which can lead
to behavioral changes in kids.
Are you accusing us
of making our son troubled?
Prao, let her explain first.
I'm sorry,
but we need to find the cause
that made Poonpun act this way.
I hope you don't mind me asking
about his behavior at home.
Because if he sees his parents
fighting at home,
he'll mimic that,
which leads to aggressive behavior
because he's mimicking what he's seen.
How should we handle him, then?
It helps to stop behaving violently
in front of your kid.
I'm counting on you both.
We'll have to help each other,
both at school and at home.
Of course, Teacher.
Good evening.
You really changed Thee, Veluree.
I don't know what you're talking about,
but it's already over
between me and Mr. Thee.
How could it be over
when he's refusing to get married?
He even disobeyed my orders.
He's never been this way before
until he met you.
You want my son so badly, don't you?
Fine.
You can have him.
But you can only take him,
and not TJ Group's assets.
If he chooses a woman like you over me,
who adopted him, then so be it.
But if you're hoping to marry into money,
then dream on.
Whoa, hey!
Easy there, or you'll end up on the floor.
You were born with a silver spoon,
so you never had to struggle.
That's why you don't know
money's true value.
How would you know
I've never had to struggle?
Has anyone ever left you before?
You're not mad at me anymore, right?
I was never mad at you.
I was the one who broke my promise.
Uncle Thee told me you love me the most,
and he also told me that
I'm luckier than him to still have my mom.
Unlike me, his mom left him.
Sorry, the number you've dialed
is currently--.
Sorry, the number you've dialed--
NOTICE OF TERMINATION OF CEO
DEAR SHAREHOLDERS AND EXECUTIVES
BEST REGARDS
MR. THEECHUDA TEERASU (CEO)
Ms. Mook!
Are you here to see Mr. Thee?
Is it true what Mrs. Anna said?
Yes. Mrs. Anna
adopted Mr. Thee as her son.
I've warned him before
that this would happen one day.
And it really did.
Mrs. Anna was very angry
that Mr. Thee's refusing to get married.
Are you sure about this, Mr. Thee?
Mrs. Anna seemed very angry.
Yes.
I've thought it through.
But you do know
what will happen after this, right?
I'm ready to accept it.
I've done everything I set out to do.
I'm ready to go back to where I belong,
Mr. Pitak.
Adopted?
From where?
Piamsuk Orphanage.
Mook!
What are you doing here?
Ms. Narin's severely ill.
She's in hospital right now.
Why are you telling me this?
That woman's got nothing to do with me.
Saifah!
Saifah, help me!
- There's a fire! Come on, come here!
- Please help my brother!
No! Let go of me!
Mr. Thee!
Do you have any idea
how much we had to suffer?!
How could you leave your kids?!
- Mr. Thee!
- How could you!
How about Tawan, honey? Did he come too?
Is your brother here too? Is he?
Where is he?
Even though I've met my mom,
I never thought of leaving you.
No! You have no choice
but to be someone I've created,
and I'm the only mother you can have.
Subtitle translation by:
Ramil Natnitiwitaya